<gamedata type="MATCH121"><fileNames gameFile="MATCH121.swf" backgroundfile="BG2.swf" soundFile="soundSet3.swf" /><fileLocations images="IMG/" sounds="SND/" /><links><item id="1" variable="gameDoneURL"><name>DragonflyTV</name><URL>pbskids.org/dragonflytv/explore/plants.html</URL><text>Want to know more? Check out the plant investigations at</text></item></links><title>Fruits</title><description>What's a fruit? It's the ripened ovary of a plant. The ovary has seeds and usually an edible covering. There are 3 kinds of fruit: fleshy, <b>drupaceous</b> (or, stone fruit), and dry. Examples of fleshy fruits are melons and apples. Drupaceous fruits have hard center stones, like peaches and plums. Dry fruits include legumes and nuts.</description><instructions>Match the fruit with its plant or tree.</instructions><parameters swapImages="1" largeFeedback="1" XCoor="50" YCoor="50" poolX="168" poolY="306" /><data><item id="1"><name>Apples</name><description>No one knows when people first began to harvest apples. Ancient Egyptians planted apple trees along the Nile. Romans cultivated 36 different kinds of apples. Wild apples grew along the Silk Road through Asia. Today, there are over 7,000 different kinds of apples!</description><files targetFile="TREE01.swf" poolFile="FRUIT01.swf" /></item><item id="2"><name>Bananas</name><description>Bananas might be our first fruit. The earliest record of bananas dates to Alexander the Great. His army ate bananas in India. Today, there are over 400 types of bananas. Bananas grow in bunches. In each bunch, there are 120 to 150 banana "fingers."</description><files targetFile="TREE02.swf" poolFile="FRUIT02.swf" /></item><item id="3"><name>Cherries</name><description>There are two kinds of cherries. sweet and sour. Sweet cherries grew in Ancient Greece 2,500 years ago. Today, there are 900 kinds of sweet cherries in colors from yellow to black. Sweet cherries produce fruit when they've been cross-pollinated by honeybees. Sour cherries don't need to be pollinated. They are "self-fertile." There are 300 kinds of sour cherries.</description><files targetFile="TREE03.swf" poolFile="FRUIT03.swf" /></item><item id="4"><name>Cocoa Beans</name><description>Cocoa trees grow in the Amazon rainforest. A cocoa tree's fruits are football-shaped pods about 12 inches long. They grow on the trunk and not on stems, like apples. The Aztecs and Mayans grew cocoa trees over 2000 years ago. They made a drink with crushed cocoa beans, cool water, chili peppers, and vanilla. It wasn't sweet like today's cocoa.</description><files targetFile="TREE04.swf" poolFile="FRUIT04.swf" /></item><item id="5"><name>Coconuts</name><description>Coconuts are the fruit of the coco palm. The coconut palm is a tree that towers anywhere from 60 to 100 feet. No one knows exactly where coconuts first grew, but they spread through the islands in the Pacific and Indian oceans by floating on ocean currents. Coconuts are a very nutritious and useful food. They provide milk, meat, sugar, and oil. They can also be used as a dish or cup!</description><files targetFile="TREE05.swf" poolFile="FRUIT05.swf" /></item><item id="6"><name>Grapes</name><description>Grapes grow natively on every continent except Antarctica. They grow on shrub-like bushes with branching vines. All grapes grow in bunches that hang off the main vine. Grapes are usually divided into green, red, white and blue grapes. There are thousands of grapes that are used to make jams, juices, and wines.</description><files targetFile="TREE06.swf" poolFile="FRUIT06.swf" /></item><item id="7"><name>Papaya</name><description>The papaya's home is southern Mexico. It isn't a tree, but a woody herb that quickly grows 6 to 12 feet tall. Today, it grows in every tropical and subtropical country. There are two kinds of papaya: Hawaiian and Mexican. You find Hawaiian papayas in supermarkets. They weigh about 1 pound. Mexican papayas are much larger and weigh up to 10 pounds.</description><files targetFile="TREE07.swf" poolFile="FRUIT07.swf" /></item><item id="8"><name>Pineapple Plants</name><description>Native Americans grew pineapples 2000 years ago. The pineapple isn't a tree, but a short tropical herb that grows up to be 3 to 5 feet tall. Its fat stem has bunches of leaves. Each leaf is 2 to 6 feet long, with a needle at the tip and sharp spines on the edges. The fruits can weigh up to 10 pounds.</description><files targetFile="TREE08.swf" poolFile="FRUIT08.swf" /></item><item id="9"><name>Pine Cones</name><description>Conifers all have pine cones. They're also known as evergreens and include pines, firs and spruce trees. There are male and female cones. Male cones are small. Female cones are large. Male cones have pollen that blow to female cones and fertilize them. Seeds in female cones grow in two years. One pine cone has about 100 seeds. The seeds are food for many birds and mammals.</description><files targetFile="TREE09.swf" poolFile="FRUIT09.swf" /></item><item id="10"><name>Pomegranates</name><description>Pomegranates have been around since ancient times. Its fruit is round and the size of a baseball. Its deep red skin is tough and leathery. Eating pomegranates is messy. Most pomegranates are consumed as juice. Pomegranate trees grow 20 feet tall. Its angular branches have spines. The leaves are shaped like spear-points. Pomegranate trees can live over 200 years!</description><files targetFile="TREE10.swf" poolFile="FRUIT10.swf" /></item><item id="11"><name>Raspberry Bushes</name><description>The raspberry is a small, dark berry that grows on a wild shrub. Its shrub is a type of bramble, which is a rough, thorny bush. Scientists are trying to develop new raspberries.</description><files targetFile="TREE11.swf" poolFile="FRUIT11.swf" /></item><item id="12"><name>Starfruit</name><description>Star Fruit is also called the carambola. Carambola is a Portuguese word meaning appetizer. Portuguese traders brought the fruit from India. It grows on a small tree with clusters of small purple flowers on leafy twigs. Like an apple, you can eat the star fruit skin and inside. If you slice the five-sided fruit cross-wise, you'll see the star shape. The taste is tart but refreshing.</description><files targetFile="TREE12.swf" poolFile="FRUIT12.swf" /></item><item id="13"><name>Walnuts</name><description>Walnuts are the oldest food from trees that humans know about. They date back at least 9,000 years. Scientists have even found roasted walnut shells that are 8,000 years old. Walnuts have been used as food, oils, medicines and dyes for thousands of years.</description><files targetFile="TREE13.swf" poolFile="FRUIT13.swf" /></item></data></gamedata>